[
  {

    "question": "What are the names of the two children the SSS save at the beginning of Zero",
    "choices": ["A. Ryu and Anri", "B. Pete and Ryu", "C. Kate and Wendy", "D. Jingo and Shizuku"],
    "answer": 3
  }, 

  {

    "question": "How many playable characters are there in the Crossbell duology",
    "choices": ["A. 11", "B. 13", "C. 10", "D. 12"],
    "answer": 3
  },

  {
      "question": "Which new enforcers are we introduced to in Azure",
      "choices": ["A. Arianrhod", "B. Campanella", "C. None", "D. Renne"],
      "answer": 2
  }, 

  {
      "question": "What's the name of the cat found at Schwarze Action",
      "choices": ["A.Coppe", "B. Celine", "C. Elizabeth", "D. Antione"],
      "answer": 3
  },

  {
      "question": "How do the SSS defeat Joachim initially",
      "choices": ["A. They don't", "B. Renne and Pater Mater help them", "C. Team up with Estelle and Joshua", "D. Arios saves them"],
      "answer": 1
  },

  {
      "question": "Which nation isn't present during the Zumrian Tarde Conference ",
      "choices": ["A. Erebonia", "B. Remiferia", "C. Liberl", "D. Ored"],
      "answer": 0
  },

  {
      "question": "What was Noel and Fran's father's name",
      "choices": ["A. Oscar", "B. Ozma", "C. Olaf", "D. Orthros"],
      "answer": 1
  },

  {
      "question": "What was Randy's alias before joining the SSS",
      "choices": ["A. Scarlet Orge", "B. Bloody", "C. Red Reaper", "D. Son of the War God"],
      "answer": 3
  },

  {
      "question": "What is the name of the NPC who sits next to Fran at the CPD",
      "choices": ["A. Kate", "B. Wendy", "C. Lynn", "D. Rebecca"],
      "answer": 1
  },

  {
      "question": "Where is Sully from initially",
      "choices": ["A. Jurai", "B. North Ambria", "C. Leman", "D. Arteria"],
      "answer": 2
  },

  {
      "question": "What's the name of the ost that plays during the Arianhod fight",
      "choices": ["A. Unfathomed Force", "B. A Barrier to Get Over", "C. Inevitable Struggle", "D. Ancient Pulsation"],
      "answer": 2
  }
 ]